Why? Why?
You've trapped me for a thousand years.
Let me in.
Why won't you let me go?
The right to reincarnate cannot be transferred.
Right?
I don't know either.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to save my daughter.
You've been lying to me from the start.
Weren't you willing to become an evil spirit for your daughter?
Fine.
I'll grant your wish.
Who exactly are you?
Come in.
Where did you go today?
Nowhere.
Before fulfilling the agreement
with your father,
I cannot leave.
You should rest early.
I'll get going.
Where are you going?
I'm going to find a place to stay.
If you haven't found a place yet,
you can keep staying here.
I... I'm too tired today.
I'm going to rest.
Make yourself at home.
Don't go.
Don't leave me.
Fate is cruel.
I can't believe you are Tang'er.
For a whole thousand years,
I have finally found you.
From now on,
I will not let you suffer the slightest harm.
Even if
it costs my life.
Attorney Gu.
Mr. Lin arranged this especially for you.
See if there's anything you're not satisfied with,
or if you need anything else.
Manager Li, actually I can...
This is a token of Mr. Lin's appreciation.
Please bear with us in your future work.
I'll leave you to it. Let me know if you need anything.
He really values you.
What should I do?
I'm a little afraid to continue.
Isn't this exactly what you wanted?
Take a look at this.
It seems I thought things were too simple.
Go back and tell him
that I will absolutely not accept a private settlement.
I will definitely take him to court.
Yingying, calm down first.
How can I calm down?
He ruined me.
If you have any conscience left,
don't bother me anymore.
I have nothing to talk about with you.
Actually, I'm not here today
to speak for Lingze.
I'm here to help you.
Ridiculous.
I think you're all working for him.
I'm not, and I never will be.
Look at this first.
The fact is that
no matter what reason you use to sue him,
he can always find a way to escape punishment.
Doing this
will only cause you more harm.
He's an absolute monster.
This...
What should I do?
Drop the charges against Lingze.
I will fight for the maximum financial compensation for you.
Please trust me.
Work with me,
and I'll avenge you.
I understand why you are worried.
It is indeed dangerous to be with that scumbag.
If I really had to be with someone like that,
it would be so disgusting.
I'd rather die.
I'll get rid of him.
I thought you couldn't fight people?
Then I'll think of another way.
Gather evidence.
Anyway, stay away from that guy from now on.
But I finally found
a chance to get close to him.
How can I give up halfway?
I have no confidence at all right now.
You will help me,
right?
I will help you with anything.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
Come in.
Is the new office okay?
It's great.
I just feel like I still don't deserve it.
You deserve it.
Thank you, Mr. Ling.
By the way,
that girl has agreed to settle privately.
Really? That was fast.
It's just that we might have to pay more compensation.
Money isn't an issue.
You always surprise me.
About us,
have you thought about it?
Mr. Ling,
I always thought
you were joking.
I never joke
about this kind of thing.
Isn't it
too fast?
Alright then.
Think about it some more.
I'll wait for your answer.
Um,
actually,
I think I can give it a try.
Really?
Xingcan, trust me.
I will definitely make you
the happiest woman in the world.
I'll introduce you to my father tonight.
Tonight?
Hello, President Ling.
Hope you've been well.
Hello, hello.
Welcome, Mr. Zhao.
How is it? Are you satisfied?
Very satisfied.
Your invitation.
We are together.
No.
Don't worry. I'm here.
This is highly collectible.
Sorry I'm late.